Finding Aid for the Rod Amateau Papers PASC.0088
UCLA Library Special Collections
- MANY LOVES OF DOBIE GILLIS, THE
  - Ugliest American, The (Show #4, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 6/4/62. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 7)
  - Unregistered Nurse, The (Show #12, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 7/3/59. Writer(s): Davis, Phil (Box 1)
  - Vocal Boy Makes Good (Show #16, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 9/7/62. Writer(s): Riesner, Dean (Box 7)
  - What Makes the Varsity Drag (Show #5, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 6/11/62. Writer(s): Nye, Bud (Box 7)
  - What's a Little Murder Between Friends (Show #1, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 5/21/62. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 7)
  - What's My Lion (Show #10, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 8/1/60. Writer(s): Riesner, Dean * Amateau, Rod (Box 3)
  - When Other Friendships Have Been Forgat (Show #33, 1961)
    - Draft script dated: 12/18/61. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 6)
  - Where is Thy Sting (Show #6, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 6/28/62. Writer(s): Kane, Joel (Box 7)
  - Where There's a Will (Show #34, 1959)
    - Draft script dated: 1/5/60. Writer(s): Allen, Ray (Box 2)
  - Who Did William Tell? (Show #17, 1962)
    - Draft script dated: 8/31/62. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 7)
  - Who Needs Elvis? (Show #1, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 6/20/60. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 3)
  - Will Success Spoil Dobie's Mother (Show #19, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 10/21/60. Writer(s): Allen, Ray * Shulman, Max (Box 3)
  - Will the Real Santa Claus Please Come Down the Chimney (Show #10)
    - Draft script dated: 7/27/62. Writer(s): Horwitt, Arnold (Box 7)
  - You Ain't Nothing But a Hound Dog (Show #2, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 6/23/60. Writer(s): Williams, Lawrence * Williams, Maggie (Box 3)
  - Zelda, Get Off My Back (Show #16, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 9/30/60. Writer(s): Williams, Lawrence & Maggie * Shulman, Max (Box 3)
- MISTER ED
  - First Meeting, The (Show #1)
    - Writer(s): O'Brien, Bob / Elinson, Irving * Shuken, Phil / Derman, Lou (Box 22)
  - Ventriloquist, The (Show #2)
    - Writer(s): Derman, Lou / Davis, Phil * Burns, William (Box 22)
- MY MOTHER, THE CAR
  - Absorba, The Geek (Prod #7527, 1965-66, v.VIII)
    - Draft script dated: 1/4/66. Writer(s): Davis, Phil (Box 22)
  - And Leave The Drive-In To Us (Prod #7515, 1965-66, v.IV)
    - Draft script dated: 9/2/65. Writer(s): Davis, Phil * Breslow, Lou / Woods, Alan (Box 21)
  - Blabbermouth, The (Prod #7528, 1965-66, v.VIII)
    - Draft script dated: 1/13/66. Writer(s): Persons, Mitch * Brooks, James L. (Box 22)
  - Burned At The Steak (Prod #7507, 1965-66, v.II)
    - Draft script dated: 7/7/65. Writer(s): Parker, Jim * Margolin, Arnold (Box 21)
  - Captain Manzini Grand Prix, The (Prod #7502, 1965-66, v.I)
    - Draft script dated: 5/27/65. Writer(s): Burns, Allan * Hayward, Chris (Box 21)
  - Come Honk Your Horn (Prod #7503, 1965-66, v.I)
    - Draft script dated: 6/4/65. Writer(s): Burns, Allan * Hayward, Chris (Box 21)
  - De-fenders, The (Prod #7501, 1965-66, v.I)
    - Draft script dated: 5/27/65. Writer(s): Burns, Allan * Hayward, Chris (Box 21)
  - Desperate Minutes (Prod #7530, 1965-66, v.VIII)
    - Draft script dated: 1/21/66. Writer(s): Davis, Phil (Box 22)
  - For Whom The Horn Honks (Prod #7511, 1965-66, v.III)
    - Draft script dated: 8/30/65. Writer(s): Kirgo, George (Box 21)
  - Hey Lady, Your Slip Isn't Showing (Prod #7509, 1965-66, v.III)
    - Draft script dated: 7/12/65. Writer(s): Koch, Tom (Box 21)
  - I Remember Mama, Why Can't You Remember Me (Prod #7506, 1965-66, v.II)
    - Draft script dated: 7/6/65. Writer(s): Parker, Jim * Margolin, Arnold (Box 21)
  - I'd Rather Do It Myself, Mother (Prod #7522, 1965-66, v.VI)
    - Draft script dated: 9/28/65. Writer(s): Linden, Stella (Box 22)
  - I'm Through Being A Nice Guy (Prod #7504, 1965-66, v.I)
    - Draft script dated: 6/9/65. Writer(s): Kirgo, George (Box 21)
  - Incredible Shrinking Car, The (Prod #7520, 1965-66, v.V)
    - Draft script dated: 11/16/65. Writer(s): Hayward, Chris * Burns, Allan (Box 22)
  - It Might As Well Be Spring As Not (Prod #7526, 1965-66, v.VII)
    - Draft script dated: 12/29/65. Writer(s): Brooks, James L. (Box 22)
  - Lassie -- I Mean, Mother Come Home! (Prod #7508, 1965-66, v.II)
    - Draft script dated: 7/15/65. Writer(s): Davis, Phil (Box 21)
  - Lights, Camera, Mother (Prod #7512, 1965-66, v.III)
    - Draft script dated: 8/12/65. Writer(s): Fox, Frank (Box 21)
  - Man From U.N.C.L.E. Louie, The (Prod #7519, 1965-66, v.V)
    - Draft script dated: 11/5/65. Writer(s): Davis, Phil (Box 22)
  - Many Happy No-Returns (Prod #7517, 1965-66, v.V)
    - Draft script dated: 9/24/65. Writer(s): Davis, Phil (Box 22)
  - My Son the Ventriloquist (Prod #7513, 1965-66, v.IV)
    - Draft script dated: 8/19/65. Writer(s): Davis, Phil (Box 21)
  - My Son, The Criminal (Prod #7523, 1965-66, v.VI)
    - Draft script dated: 12/7/65. Writer(s): Davis, Phil (Box 22)
  - My Son, The Judge (Prod #7518, 1965-66, v.V)
    - Draft script dated: 9/30/65. Writer(s): Garrett, Lila / Kahn, Bernie * Davis, Phil (Box 22)
  - Over The Hill To The Junkyard (Prod #7525, 1965-66, v.VII)
    - Draft script dated: 12/21/65. Writer(s): Davis, Phil (Box 22)
  - Riddler On The Roof (Prod #7521, 1965-66, v.VI)
    - Draft script dated: 11/26/65. Writer(s): Davis, Phil (Box 22)
  - Shine On Shine On, Honey Moon (Prod #7514, 1965-66, v.IV)
    - Draft script dated: 8/27/65. Writer(s): Davis, Phil (Box 21)
  - TV Or Not TV (Prod #7510, 1965-66, v.III)
    - Draft script dated: 7/27/65. Writer(s): Allen, Ray (Box 21)
  - Unreasonable Facsimile, An (Prod #7524, 1965-66, v.VII)
    - Draft script dated: 12/15/65. Writer(s): Parker, Jim * Margolin, Arnold (Box 22)
  - What Makes Auntie Freeze (Prod #7505, 1965-66, v.II)
    - Draft script dated: 6/24/65. Writer(s): Dennis, Robert C. * Barret, Earl (Box 21)
  - When You Wish Upon A Car (Prod #7529, 1965-66, v.VIII)
    - Draft script dated: 1/17/66. Writer(s): Barbour, John * Mitchell, Whitey (Box 22)
  - You Can't Get There From Here (Prod #7516, 1965-66, v.IV)
    - Draft script dated: 9/10/65. Writer(s): Parker, Jim * Margolin, Arnold (Box 21)
- O.K. CRACKERBY!
  - 3 + 1 = 1 (Show #8804, v.I, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 6/25/65. Writer(s): Davis, Phil (Box 15)
  - Bitter Ravioli (Show #8816, v.IV, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 10/26/65. Writer(s): Allardice, James * Adair, Tom (Box 15)
  - Crackerby and the Cuckoo Game (Show #8813, v.IV, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 9/23/65. Writer(s): O'Hallaren, Bill (Box 15)
  - Crackerby For Treasurer (Show #8808, v.II, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 8/27/65. Writer(s): Baer, Richard (Box 15)
  - Crackerby Stops The Press (Show #8815, v.IV, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 10/15/65. Writer(s): O'Hallaren, Bill (Box 15)
  - Crackerby's Tutor (Show #8806, v.II, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 7/19/65. Writer(s): Margolin, Arnold * Parker, Jim (Box 15)
  - Crackerby's Unfinished Symphony (Show #8807, v.II, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 10/11/65. Writer(s): Menzies, James (Box 15)
  - Griffin Story, The (Show #8803, v.I, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 6/17/65. Writer(s): Dennis, Robert C. * Barret, Earl (Box 15)
  - No Deposit, No Return (Show #8814, v.IV, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 10/4/65. Writer(s): Allardice, James * Adair, Tom (Box 15)
  - Ol' Sam (Show #8810, v.III, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 9/2/65. Writer(s): Webster, Tony * O'Hallaren, Bill (Box 15)
  - Operation Susan (Show #8817, v.IV, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 11/1/65. Writer(s): Eustis, Rich * Rodgers, Al (Box 15)
  - Smile and the World.. (Show #8805, v.II, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 7/7/65. Writer(s): Balzer, George (Box 15)
  - St. John Raid, The (Show #8811, v.III, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 9/13/65. Writer(s): O'Hallaren, Bill (Box 15)
  - Wellecliffe Story, The (Show #8802, v.I, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 6/21/65. Writer(s): Burrows, Abe * Ryan, Ted (Box 15)
  - Who Was That Lady You Saw Me With (Show #8809, v.III, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 8/20/65. Writer(s): Ryan, Terry (Box 15)
  - Woodman, Spare That Family Tree (Show #8812, v.III, 1965-66)
    - Draft script dated: 9/28/65. Writer(s): Parker, Jim * Margolin, Arnold (Box 15)
- PHIL SILVERS SHOW, THE
  - 75 1/2 Trombones (Show #2, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 4/26/63. Writer(s): Sharp, Phil (Box 19)
  - Auntie Up (Show #27, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 1/30/64. Writer(s): Raynor, Bill * Wilder, Myles (Box 20)
  - Beauty and the Least (Show #10, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 6/27/63. Writer(s): Starr, Ben (Box 19)
  - Big Brother Is Watching You (Show #37, 1963, Not Filmed)
    - Draft script dated: 12/16/63. Writer(s): Amateau, Rod (Box 20)
  - Birthday Boy, The (Show #3, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 5/2/63. Writer(s): Simon, Danny (Box 19)
  - Buy Low, Sell High (Show #31, 1963, Not Filmed)
    - Draft script dated: 3/9/64. Writer(s): Glickman, Will * Zelinka, Sydney (Box 20)
  - Cyrano De Grafton (Show #14, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 8/7/63. Writer(s): Starr, Ben (Box 19)
  - Funny Thing Happened to Me on the Way to the Coffee Break, A (Show #16, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 8/21/63. Writer(s): Sharp, Phil (Box 19)
  - Grafton's My Name, Football's My Game (Show #28, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 2/5/64. Writer(s): Jurist, Ed * Kane, Robert G. (Box 20)
  - Great Fork-Lift Contest, The (Show #8, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 6/17/63. Writer(s): Marks, Lawrence (Box 19)
  - Harry Today, Gone Tomorrow (Show #1, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 5/10/63. Writer(s): Starr, Ben (Box 19)
  - Harry Who? (Show #15, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 9/3/63. Writer(s): Jurist, Ed * Nye, Bud (Box 19)
  - Harry, The Good Neighbor (Show #25, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 1/9/64. Writer(s): James, Ed * Jacobs, Seaman (Box 20)
  - Have I Got A Boy For You (Show #17, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 8/26/63. Writer(s): Jurist, Ed * Nye, Bud (Box 19)
  - How to Succeed in Business Without Crying (Show #19, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 10/2/63. Writer(s): Starr, Ben (Box 19)
  - Hustle While You Work (Show #35, 1963, Not Filmed)
    - Draft script dated: 9/23/63. Writer(s): Jurist, Ed * Nye, Bud (Box 20)
  - It's Better To Have Loved And Lost -- Much Better (Show #33, 1963, Not Filmed)
    - Draft script dated: 11/4/63. Writer(s): Sharp, Phil (Box 20)
  - Keep A Light Burning In The $2 Window, Mother (Show #36, 1963, Not Filmed)
    - Draft script dated: 9/10/63. Writer(s): Starr, Ben * Marks, Laurence (Box 20)
  - Keep Cool (Show #29, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 2/17/64. Writer(s): Marks, Laurence (Box 20)
  - Las Vegas Was My Mother's Maiden Name (Show #21, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 10/24/63. Writer(s): Starr, Ben (Box 20)
  - Leave It To Harry (Show #23, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 12/26/63. Writer(s): Marks, Laurence (Box 20)
  - Little Old Gluemaker, Me! (Show #9, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 7/3/63. Writer(s): Nye, Bud * Jurist, Ed (Box 19)
  - Man, It's Like Progress (Show #4, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 6/6/63. Writer(s): Russell, A.J. * Solomon, Lou (Box 19)
  - Moonlight And Dozes (Show #7, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 6/26/63. Writer(s): Starr, Ben (Box 19)
  - Move Forward With Vigah (Show #18, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 9/23/63. Writer(s): Russell, A.J. (Box 19)
  - Pay The $2 (Show #24, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 1/6/64. Writer(s): Marks, Laurence (Box 20)
  - Smile Harry, You're On Candid Camera (Show #22, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 12/16/63. Writer(s): Kane, Robert G. * Lewis, Al (Box 20)
  - Somebody Upstairs Likes Me (Show #6, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 6/20/63. Writer(s): Sharp, Phil (Box 19)
  - Son of Pygmalion, The (Show #20, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 10/21/63. Writer(s): Sharp, Phil * Hinkley, Don (Box 19)
  - Stop the Factory, I Wanna Get Off (Show #11, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 7/5/63. Writer(s): Starr, Ben (Box 19)
  - Sweet Smell of Defeat (synopsis, 1963, Not Filmed)
    - Draft script dated: 7/8/63. Writer(s): Starr, Ben * Marks, Laurence (Box 20)
  - Take Her, She's Tall (Show #26, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 1/27/64. Writer(s): Starr, Ben (Box 20)
  - Take One Father Out Of Petty Cash (Show #34, 1963, Not Filmed)
    - Draft script dated: 6/21/63. Writer(s): Starr, Ben (Box 20)
  - Triple Indemnity (Show #5, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 5/27/63. Writer(s): Jurist, Ed * Nye, Bud (Box 19)
  - Vanity, Thy Name Is Harry (Show #30, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 2/27/64. Writer(s): Marks, Laurence (Box 20)
  - Vote Yes On No (Show #32, 1963, Not Filmed)
    - Draft script dated: 5/21/63. Writer(s): Starr, Ben (Box 20)
  - Who Do Voodo? Harry Do! (Show #12, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 7/30/63. Writer(s): Starr, Ben (Box 19)
  - Will The Real Harry Grafton Please Stand Up (Show #13, 1963)
    - Draft script dated: 8/1/63. Writer(s): Starr, Ben (Box 19)
- PICTURE WINDOW
  - Hand Me Down (Pilot, 1960)
    - Draft script dated: 1/11/60. Writer(s): Shulman, Max (Box 20)